thehunter.com 2012-11-05

# theHunter - Privacy Policy

Date of Last Revision: February 9, 2009

theHunter's Privacy Policy is designed to help you understand how we collect and use the personal information you decide to share, and help you make informed decisions when using theHunter, located at www.thehunter.com and its directly associated domains (collectively, "theHunter" or "Website").

By using or accessing theHunter, you are accepting the practices described in this Privacy Policy.

## 1\. The Information We Collect

When you visit theHunter you provide us with two types of information: personal information you knowingly choose to disclose that is collected by us and Web Site use information collected by us as you interact with our Web Site.

When you register with theHunter, you provide us with certain personal information, such as your name, your email address, and any other personal or preference information that you provide to us.

When you enter theHunter, we collect your browser type and IP address. This information is gathered for all theHunter visitors. In addition, we store certain information from your browser using "cookies." A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user's computer tied to information about the user. We use session ID cookies to confirm that users are logged in. These cookies terminate once the user closes the browser.

When you use theHunter, you may set up your personal profile, form relationships, send messages, form groups, set up events, add applications, and transmit information through various channels. We collect this information so that we can provide you the service and offer personalized features. In most cases, we retain it so that, for instance, you can return to view prior messages you have sent or easily see your friend list. When you update information, we usually keep a backup copy of the prior version for a reasonable period of time to enable reversion to the prior version of that information.

You post User Content (as defined in the theHunter Terms of Use) on the Site at your own risk. Although we allow you to set privacy options that limit access to your pages, please be aware that no security measures are perfect or impenetrable. We cannot control the actions of other Users with whom you may choose to share your pages and information. Therefore, we cannot and do not guarantee that User Content you post on the Site will not be viewed by unauthorized persons. We are not responsible for circumvention of any privacy settings or security measures contained on the Site. You understand and acknowledge that, even after removal, copies of User Content may remain viewable in cached and archived pages or if other Users have copied or stored your User Content.

Any improper collection or misuse of information provided on theHunter is a violation of the theHunter Terms of Service and should be reported to us at [privacy@thehunter.com](mailto:privacy@thehunter.com).

If you choose to use our invitation service to tell a friend about our site, we will ask you for information needed to send the invitation, such as your friend's email address. We will automatically send your friend a one-time email or instant message inviting him or her to visit the site. theHunter stores this information to send this one-time invitation, to register a friend connection if your invitation is accepted, and to track the success of our referral program. Your friend may contact us at [info@thehunter.com](mailto:info@thehunter.com) to request that we remove this information from our database.

theHunter may also collect information about you from other sources, such as newspapers, blogs, instant messaging services, and other users of the theHunter service through the operation of the service (e.g., photo tags) in order to provide you with more useful information and a more personalized experience.

Finally, we collect financial information as set out in Section 5 of this Privacy Policy. We do not use this financial information for any purpose other than processing payments to Expansive Worlds AB, the publisher of theHunter. The financial information that you enter to purchase a membership is not stored by theHunter or Expansive Worlds AB, but, instead, is retained by our payments processing vendor for the purpose of processing credit card payments made to Expansive Worlds AB. 

If personal information is not provided to us, then theHunter may not agree theHunter Club membership and may not be able to provide access to certain content and functionality on theHunter website, or to provide other information, products or services which may be requested.

By using theHunter, you are consenting to have your personal data transferred to and processed in the United States and the European Union.

## 2\. Children Under Age 13

theHunter does not knowingly collect or solicit personal information from anyone under the age of 13 or knowingly allow such persons to register. If you are under 13, please do not attempt to register for theHunter or send any information about yourself to us, including your name, address, telephone number, or email address. No one under age 13 may provide any personal information to or on theHunter. In the event that we learn that we have collected personal information from a child under age 13 without verification of parental consent, we will delete that information as quickly as possible. If you believe that we might have any information from or about a child under age 13, please contact us at [info@thehunter.com](mailto:info@thehunter.com).

## 3\. Children between the Ages of 13 and 18

We recommend that minors over the age of 13 ask their parents for permission before sending any information about themselves to anyone over the Internet.

## 4\. Use of Information Obtained by theHunter

When you register with theHunter, you create your own profile and privacy settings. Your profile information, as well as your name, email and photo, are displayed to people in the networks specified in your privacy settings to enable you to connect with people on theHunter. We may occasionally use your name and email address to send you notifications regarding new services offered by theHunter that we think you may find valuable.  
Profile information is used by theHunter primarily to be presented back to and edited by you when you access the service and to be presented to others permitted to view that information by your privacy settings. In some cases where your privacy settings permit it (e.g., posting to your wall), other users of theHunter may be able to supplement your profile.

Profile information you submit to theHunter will be available to users of theHunter who belong to at least one of the networks you allow to access the information through your privacy settings. Your name, network names, and profile picture thumbnail will be available in search results across the theHunter network and those limited pieces of information may be made available to third party search engines. This is primarily so your friends can find you and send a friend request. People who see your name in searches, however, will not be able to access your profile information unless they have a relationship to you (friend, friend of friend, member of your networks, etc.) that allows such access based on your privacy settings.

theHunter may send you service-related announcements from time to time through the general operation of the service. theHunter reserves the right to send you notices about your account even if you opt out of all voluntary email notifications.

theHunter may use information in your profile without identifying you as an individual to third parties. We do this for purposes such as aggregating how many people in a network like a band or movie and personalizing advertisements and promotions so that we can provide you theHunter. We believe this benefits you. You can know more about the world around you and, where there are advertisements, they're more likely to be interesting to you. For example, if you put a favorite movie in your profile, we might serve you an advertisement highlighting a screening of a similar one in your town. But we don't tell the movie company who you are.  
We may use information about you that we collect from other sources, including but not limited to newspapers and Internet sources such as blogs, instant messaging services, theHunter Platform developers and other users of theHunter, to supplement your profile. Where such information is used, we generally allow you to specify in your privacy settings that you do not want this to be done or to take other actions that limit the connection of this information to your profile (e.g., removing photo tag links).

## 5\. Financial Information

As noted in Section 1, if you decide to purchase a membership and are 18 years old or older, your full name, email address, and credit card billing information, including mailing address will be required at the time of purchase. That information is not stored by theHunter, and, instead, is collected and stored by our payments processing vendor for the purpose of processing payments made to Expansive Worlds AB. That information is safeguarded with appropriate security, and it will not be used for other purposes. Furthermore, our payments processing vendor has agreed to maintain the confidentiality, security, and integrity of the personal and financial information it obtains from theHunter website, and only to use this information on our behalf. Our financial institution is bound by all applicable privacy laws relating to the provision of financial services.

If you decide to purchase a membership and are under the age of 18 and over the age of 13, your parent's full name, email address, and credit card billing information including mailing address will be required at the time of purchase. That information is not stored by theHunter, and, instead, is collected and stored by our payments processing vendor for the purpose of processing payments made to Expansive Worlds AB. That information is safeguarded with appropriate security, and it will not be used for other purposes. Furthermore, our payments processing vendor has agreed to maintain the confidentiality, security, and integrity of the personal and financial information it obtains from theHunter website, and only to use this information on our behalf. Our financial institution is bound by all applicable privacy laws relating to the provision of financial services.

## 6\. Sharing Your Information with Third Parties

theHunter's community service is about sharing information with others ï¿½ friends and people in your networks ï¿½ while providing you with privacy settings that restrict other users from accessing your information. We allow you to choose the information you provide to friends and networks through theHunter. Our network architecture and your privacy settings allow you to make informed choices about who has access to your information. We do not provide contact information to third party marketers without your permission. We share your information with third parties only in limited circumstances where we believe such sharing is 1) reasonably necessary to offer the service, 2) legally required or, 3) permitted by you. For example:

  * Your news feeds may aggregate the information you provide and make it available to your friends and network members according to your privacy settings.
  * We may provide information to service providers to help us bring you the services we offer. Specifically, we may use third parties to facilitate our business, such as to host the service at a co-location facility for servers, to send out email updates about theHunter, to remove repetitive information from our user lists, to process payments for products or services, to offer an online job application process, or to provide search results or links (including sponsored links). In connection with these offerings and business operations, our service providers may have access to your personal information for use for a limited time in connection with these business activities. Where we utilize third parties for the processing of any personal information, we implement reasonable contractual and technical protections limiting the use of that information to the theHunter-specified purposes.
  * If you, your friends, or members of your network use any third-party applications developed using the theHunter Platform ("Platform Applications"), those Platform Applications may access and share certain information about you with others in accordance with your privacy settings. In addition, third party developers who have created and operate Platform Applications ("Platform Developers"), may also have access to your personal information (excluding your contact information) if you permit Platform Applications to access your data. Before allowing any Platform Developer to make any Platform Application available to you, theHunter requires the Platform Developer to enter into an agreement which, among other things, requires them to respect your privacy settings and strictly limits their collection, use, and storage of your information. However, while we have undertaken contractual and technical steps to restrict possible misuse of such information by such Platform Developers, we of course cannot and do not guarantee that all Platform Developers will abide by such agreements. Please note that theHunter does not screen or approve Platform Developers and cannot control how such Platform Developers use any personal information that they may obtain in connection with Platform Applications. In addition, Platform Developers may require you to sign up to their own terms of service, privacy policies or other policies, which may give them additional rights or impose additional obligations on you, so please make sure to review these terms and policies carefully before using any Platform Application. You can report any suspected misuse of information through the theHunter Platform and we will investigate any such claim and take appropriate action against the Platform Developer up to and including terminating their participation in the theHunter Platform and/or other formal legal action.
  * We occasionally provide demonstration accounts that allow non-users a glimpse into the theHunter world. Such accounts have only limited capabilities (e.g., messaging is disabled) and passwords are changed regularly to limit possible misuse.
  * We may be required to disclose user information pursuant to lawful requests, such as subpoenas or court orders, or in compliance with applicable laws. We do not reveal information until we have a good faith belief that an information request by law enforcement or private litigants meets applicable legal standards. Additionally, we may share account or other information when we believe it is necessary to comply with law, to protect our interests or property, to prevent fraud or other illegal activity perpetrated through the theHunter service or using the theHunter name, or to prevent imminent bodily harm. This may include sharing information with other companies, lawyers, agents or government agencies.
  * We let you choose to share information with marketers or electronic commerce providers through sponsored groups or other on-site offers.
  * We may offer stores or provide services jointly with other companies on theHunter. You can tell when another company is involved in any store or service provided on theHunter, and we may share customer information with that company in connection with your use of that store or service.
  * Like many other websites that interact with third party sites, we may receive some information even if you are logged out from theHunter, or that pertains to non-theHunter users, from those sites in conjunction with the technical operation of the system. In cases where theHunter receives information on users that are not logged in, or on non-theHunter users, we do not attempt to associate it with individual theHunter accounts and will discard it.
  * If the ownership of all or substantially all of the theHunter business, or individual business units owned by theHunter, Inc., were to change, your user information may be transferred to the new owner so the service can continue operations. In any such transfer of information, your user information would remain subject to the promises made in any pre-existing Privacy Policy. When you use theHunter, certain information you post or share with third parties (e.g., a friend or someone in your network), such as personal information, comments, messages, photos, videos, or other information, may be shared with other users in accordance with the privacy settings you select. All such sharing of information is done at your own risk. Please keep in mind that if you disclose personal information in your profile or when posting comments, messages, photos, videos, or other items, this information may become publicly available.

## 7\. Links

theHunter may contain links to other websites. We are of course not responsible for the privacy practices of other web sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site to read the privacy statements of each and every web site that collects personally identifiable information. This Privacy Policy applies solely to information collected by theHunter.

## 8\. Third Party Advertising

Advertisements that may appear on theHunter are sometimes delivered (or "served") directly to users by third party advertisers. They automatically receive your IP address when this happens. These third party advertisers may also download cookies to your computer, or use other technologies such as JavaScript and "web beacons" (also known as "1x1 gifs") to measure the effectiveness of their ads and to personalize advertising content. Doing this allows the advertising network to recognize your computer each time they send you an advertisement in order to measure the effectiveness of their ads and to personalize advertising content. In this way, they may compile information about where individuals using your computer or browser saw their advertisements and determine which advertisements are clicked. theHunter does not have access to or control of the cookies that may be placed by the third party advertisers. Third party advertisers have no access to your contact information stored on theHunter unless you choose to share it with them.

This privacy policy covers the use of cookies by theHunter and does not cover the use of cookies or other tracking technologies by any of its advertisers.

## 9\. Changing or Removing Information

Access and control over most personal information on theHunter is readily available through the profile editing tools. theHunter users may modify or delete any of their profile information at any time by logging into their account. Information will be updated immediately. Individuals who wish to deactivate their theHunter account may do so on the My Account page. Removed information may persist in backup copies for a reasonable period of time but will not be generally available to members of theHunter.

Where you make use of the communication features of the service to share information with other individuals on theHunter, however, (e.g., sending a personal message to another theHunter user) you generally cannot remove such communications.

## 10\. Security

theHunter takes appropriate precautions to protect our users' information. Your account information is located on a secured server behind a firewall. When you enter sensitive information (such as credit card number or your password), we encrypt that information using secure socket layer technology (SSL). (To learn more about SSL, go to <http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Secure_Sockets_Layer>). Because email and instant messaging are not recognized as secure communications, we request that you not send private information to us by email or instant messaging services. If you have any questions about the security of theHunter Web Site, please contact us at [privacy@thehunter.com](mailto:privacy@thehunter.com).

## 11\. Terms of Use, Notices and Revisions

Your use of theHunter, and any disputes arising from it, is subject to this Privacy Policy as well as our Terms of Use and all of its dispute resolution provisions including limitation on damages and choice of law. We reserve the right to change our Privacy Policy and our Terms of Use at any time. Non-material changes and clarifications will take effect immediately, and material changes will take effect within 30 days of their posting on this site. If we make changes, we will post them and will indicate at the top of this page the policy's new effective date. If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you here, by email, or through notice on our home page. We encourage you to refer to this policy on an ongoing basis so that you understand our current privacy policy. Unless stated otherwise, our current privacy policy applies to all information that we have about you and your account.

## 12\. Contacting the Web Site

If you have any questions about this privacy policy, please contact us at [privacy@thehunter.com](mailto:privacy@thehunter.com). You may also contact us by mail at Expansive Worlds AB, Åsögatan 108, 118 29 Stockholm, SWEDEN.
